<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!--
    Generator for metainfo & .desktop files:
    https://www.freedesktop.org/software/appstream/metainfocreator/#/
-->
<component type="desktop-application">
    <id>com.adilhanney.saber</id>

    <name>Saber</name>
    <summary>The notes app built for handwriting</summary>
    <url type="homepage">https://github.com/saber-notes/saber</url>
    <url type="bugtracker">https://github.com/saber-notes/saber/issues</url>
    <url type="donation">https://github.com/sponsors/adil192</url>
    <url type="translate">https://hosted.weblate.org/engage/saber-notes/</url>
    <url type="vcs-browser">https://github.com/saber-notes/saber</url>

    <developer id="com.adilhanney">
        <name>Adil Hanney</name>
    </developer>

    <branding>
        <color type="primary" scheme_preference="light">#fff6da</color>
        <color type="primary" scheme_preference="dark">#705600</color>
    </branding>

    <metadata_license>MIT</metadata_license>
    <project_license>GPL-3.0-only</project_license>

    <supports>
        <control>pointing</control>
        <control>keyboard</control>
        <control>touch</control>
    </supports>

    <recommends>
        <control>tablet</control>
        <internet>always</internet>
    </recommends>

    <requires>
        <display_length compare="ge">360</display_length>
    </requires>

    <provides>
        <mediatype>application/sbn</mediatype>
        <mediatype>application/json</mediatype>
        <mediatype>text/*</mediatype>

        <mediatype>application/sbn2</mediatype>
        <mediatype>application/octet-stream</mediatype>

        <mediatype>application/sba</mediatype>
        <mediatype>application/zip</mediatype>
    </provides>

    <description>
        <!--
        DO NOT EDIT.
        Any modifications will be overwritten.
        This <description/> tag is generated by bump_version.dart from `metadata/*/full_description.txt`.
        -->
        <p>
            Saber is the notes app built for handwriting.
        </p>
        <p>
            It's designed to be as simple and intuitive as possible, while still delivering unique features that you'll actually use. Additionally, Saber is available across all your devices, large and small, and syncs between them seamlessly.
        </p>
        <p>
            Notably, it can invert your notes when you're in dark mode. This allows you to write with white ink on a black background, which is much easier on the eyes in low-light environments like when the teacher turns off the lights in class.
        </p>
        <p>
            Images and PDFs are also inverted, so you can still use a digital printout or a textbook without the fuss.
        </p>
        <p>
            Saber uses a dual-password system to protect your notes from anyone but you, even if they have complete control over the server. You can safely store your notes on the official Saber server, another server, or even host your own!
        </p>
        <p>
            The app is completely open-source so that anyone can view the source code and see exactly what it's doing and how it handles your data. Many other note-taking apps are closed-source and proprietary, meaning that their inner workings are a mystery to the public.
        </p>
        <p>
            As someone who studies maths, highlighting multi-line equations was always a hassle with other apps, where the highlighter would change color when it overlapped with itself. Another problem I had was that in some apps, the highlighter would render on top of the text, fading it out and making it hard to read.
        </p>
        <p>
            Saber's highlighter has no such issues. It utilizes canvas compositing to render the highlighter in a way that is consistent with/better than traditional paper, where it handles overlaps and maintains color consistency.
        </p>
        <p>
            Saber has everything you need to keep your notes organized. Create folders inside folders inside folders to your heart's content with no limit on the number of nested folders. And even though a note may be buried deep within a nested folder, you can still access it easily with your most recent notes always available on the home screen.
        </p>
        <p>
            Discover a whole new way to capture and organize your thoughts with Saber. Whether you're a student, professional, or creative mind, Saber is your trusted companion for digital handwriting. Download now and let your ideas flow freely!
        </p>

        <p xml:lang="cs">
            Saber je aplikace pro psaní poznámek uzpůsobená pro ruční psaní.
        </p>
        <p xml:lang="cs">
            Je navržena pro nejjednodušší a nejintuitivnější možné používání, přičemž stále nabízí unikátní funkce, které opravdu využijete. Navíc je Saber dostupný napříč všemi vašimi zařízeními, velkými i malými, mezi nimiž se bez povšimnutí synchronizuje.
        </p>
        <p xml:lang="cs">
            Je na místě poznamenat, že umí invertovat vaše poznámky, pokud jste v temném módu. To vám umožňuje psát bílým inkoustem na černém pozadí, což je daleko příjemnější pro oči v prostředí s nedostatkem světla, jako když učitel ve třídě vypne osvětlení. Obrázky a PDF jsou také invertovány, takže stále můžete bez problému používat digitální výtisky nebo učebnice.
        </p>
        <p xml:lang="cs">
            Saber používá systém dvou hesel, aby ochránil vaše poznámky před kýmkoliv kromě vás, i kdyby měl kompletní přístup k serveru. Můžete bezpečně ukládat své poznámky na oficiální server aplikace Saber, jiný server či dokonce pro tyto účely provozovat svůj vlastní server!
        </p>
        <p xml:lang="cs">
            Aplikace má kompletně otevřené zdrojové kódy, takže si je každý může prohlédnout a přesně vidět, co aplikace dělá a jakým způsobem jsou zpracovává vaše data. Spousta dalších aplikací pro pořizování poznámek má uzavřené zdrojové kódy a je proprietární, což znamená, že co se děje uvnitř, je pro veřejnost záhadou.
        </p>
        <p xml:lang="cs">
            Jako někdo, kdo studuje matematiku, mohu říct, že pro mě vždy bylo utrpení zvýrazňovat víceřádkové rovnice v jiných aplikacích, kde zvýrazňovač mění barvu po přetažení již zvýrazněné části. Další problém, který jsem měl v některých aplikacích, spočíval v tom, že se zvýrazňovač vykresloval nad textem, takže se text ztrácel a špatně se četl. Zvýrazňovač aplikace Saber těmito neduhy netrpí. Využívá kompozice plátna k vykreslování zvýrazňovače způsobem, který je konzistentní s tradičním papírem, ba možná i lepší, jelikož řeší překrývání a udržuje konzistenci barev.
        </p>
        <p xml:lang="cs">
            Saber má vše, co potřebujete k tomu, abyste dokázali organizovat své poznámky. Tvořte složky uvnitř složek uvnitř složek, jak jen chcete bez omezení na počet zanořených složek. Ačkoliv může být poznámka pohřbena hluboko uvnitř vnořené složky, pořád k ní můžete jednoduše přistoupit, jelikož jsou nejnovější poznámky vždy k dispozici na domovské obrazovce.
        </p>
        <p xml:lang="cs">
            Objevte zcela nový způsob zaznamenávání a organizace vašich myšlenek s aplikací Saber. Ať již jste student, profesionál nebo kreativní duše, Saber je vaším důvěryhodným společníkem pro digitální psaní. Stáhněte si jej nyní a nechte volně plynout své nápady!
        </p>

        <p xml:lang="ru">
            Как разработчик Saber, я очень рад представить Вам приложение с революционным способом ведения заметок. Saber — это идеальное приложение для создания рукописных заметок, разработанное для того, чтобы поднять Ваши навыки ведения заметок до новых высот! Овладейте искусством рукописного ввода и раскройте свой творческий потенциал с помощью этого многофункционального приложения, основанного на передовых технологиях. Интуитивно понятный и современный интерфейс Saber позволяет легко делать заметки, рисовать схемы или точно комментировать PDF-файлы.
        </p>
        <p xml:lang="ru">
            Когда я начал делать цифровые заметки, я не мог найти никаких конфиденциальных приложений с открытым исходным кодом, которые соответствовали бы моим требованиям, поэтому мне пришлось использовать платное приложение. Я решил создать Saber, чтобы дать людям выбор конфиденциального приложения с открытым исходным кодом, которому они могут доверять. Saber имеет полностью открытый исходный код, а это означает, что любой может проверить код, чтобы убедиться, что он безопасен и приватен. Saber шифрует Ваши данные и может синхронизироваться с любым совместимым сервером по вашему выбору, предоставляя вам полный контроль над вашими данными.
        </p>
        <p xml:lang="ru">
            Вам нравится делать заметки на планшете, а затем переносить их на компьютер? Или, может быть, вы предпочитаете набирать заметки на ноутбуке, а затем комментировать их на планшете? Каким бы ни был ваш рабочий процесс, Saber обеспечит вам кроссплатформенную поддержку, позволяя вам получать доступ к своим заметкам в любое время, в любом месте и на любом устройстве. Saber доступен на Android, iOS, Windows, macOS и Linux, при этом ваши заметки автоматически синхронизируются на всех ваших устройствах. А если вы не в сети, Saber автоматически синхронизирует ваши заметки, как только вы снова подключитесь к сети.
        </p>
        <p xml:lang="ru">
            Saber оснащён лучшим цифровым маркером, который вы когда-либо использовали. Вам когда-нибудь приходилось выделять несколько линий, но вам не нравилось, как маркер накладывался друг на друга и менял цвет? Saber использует усовершенствованную обработку графики для обработки перекрытий и сохранения согласованности цветов пера, что даёт вам лучший опыт работы с маркером, чем традиционная бумага.
        </p>
        <p xml:lang="ru">
            В Saber есть всё, что вам нужно для систематизации ваших заметок. Создавайте папки внутри папок внутри папок сколько душе угодно без ограничения количества вложенных папок. И даже если заметка может быть скрыта глубоко во вложенной папке, вы всё равно можете легко получить к ней доступ, так как ваши самые последние заметки всегда доступны на главном экране.
        </p>
        <p xml:lang="ru">
            Saber может интеллектуально инвертировать ваши заметки, когда включен тёмный режим. Это означает, что вы можете использовать весь процесс ведения заметок в тёмном режиме, включая ваши изображения, в плавном и связанном интерфейсе в условиях низкой освещённости.
        </p>
        <p xml:lang="ru">
            Откройте для себя совершенно новый способ фиксации и систематизации мыслей с помощью Saber. Независимо от того, являетесь ли вы студентом, профессионалом или творческим человеком, Saber станет вашим надёжным помощником в цифровом рукописном вводе. Загрузите сейчас и дайте волю своим идеям!
        </p>

        <p xml:lang="vi">
            Saber là ứng dụng được tối ưu hóa cho ghi chú viết tay.
        </p>
        <p xml:lang="vi">
            Ứng dụng được thiết kế đơn giản và trực quan nhất có thể, đồng thời cung cấp các tính năng độc đáo mà bạn thực sự cần dùng. Saber có sẵn trên mọi thiết bị của bạn, dù lớn hay nhỏ, và đồng bộ hóa liền mạch.
        </p>
        <p xml:lang="vi">
            Đặc biệt, Saber có thể đảo màu ghi chú của bạn khi bạn ở chế độ tối. Điều này cho phép bạn viết bằng mực trắng trên nền đen, giúp bảo vệ mắt trong môi trường thiếu sáng.
        </p>
        <p xml:lang="vi">
            Hình ảnh và tệp PDF cũng sẽ được đảo màu, giúp bạn thoải mái sử dụng giáo trình hay các sách in điện tử.
        </p>
        <p xml:lang="vi">
            Saber sử dụng hệ thống mật khẩu kép để bảo vệ bản ghi chú của bạn khỏi bất kỳ ai ngoài bạn, ngay cả khi họ có toàn quyền kiểm soát máy chủ. Bạn có thể an tâm lưu trữ ghi chú trên máy chủ Saber chính thức, trên một máy chủ khác hoặc thậm chí tự host máy chủ của riêng mình!
        </p>
        <p xml:lang="vi">
            Ứng dụng này có mã nguồn mở, bất kỳ ai cũng có thể xem mã nguồn, biết chính xác ứng dụng đang làm gì và xử lý dữ liệu của bạn ra sao. Rất nhiều ứng dụng ghi chú khác là mã nguồn đóng và độc quyền, nghĩa là cách thức hoạt động nội bộ của chúng là một bí ẩn đối với công chúng.
        </p>
        <p xml:lang="vi">
            Đối với các ứng dụng khác, việc dùng bút dạ quang để highlight các phương trình Toán dài dòng luôn rất phiền phức, khi mà màu highlight bị thay đổi tại những chỗ đoạn màu đè lên nhau. Một vấn đề khác tôi từng gặp phải ở một vài app là màu highlight lại được vẽ đè lên trên dòng chữ, làm cho chữ bị mờ đi và khó đọc.
        </p>
        <p xml:lang="vi">
            Tính năng highlight của Saber không gặp những vấn đề này. Saber sử dụng kỹ thuật canvas compositing để hiển thị màu highlight một cách nhất quán/tốt hơn so với trên giấy thật, nơi app tự xử lý các phần nét đè lên nhau và giữ được độ đồng nhất hoàn hảo của màu sắc.
        </p>
        <p xml:lang="vi">
            Saber có mọi thứ bạn cần để giữ cho ghi chú của bạn ngăn nắp. Bạn có thể tạo các thư mục lồng nhau bao nhiêu tùy thích. Và dù một bản ghi chú có nằm sâu trong thư mục lồng nhau, bạn vẫn có thể mở nó dễ dàng ở mục "Các ghi chú mở gần đây", nó luôn có sẵn trên màn hình chính.
        </p>
        <p xml:lang="vi">
            Khám phá một phương thức hoàn toàn mới để ghi chép và sắp xếp mọi luồng suy nghĩ với Saber. Dù bạn là sinh viên, người đi làm, hay một người có tư duy sáng tạo, Saber sẽ luôn là bạn đồng hành đáng tin cậy của bạn cho việc ghi chép kỹ thuật số. Hãy tải xuống ngay hôm nay và để cho những ý tưởng của bạn tha hồ tuôn trào!
        </p>

        <p xml:lang="zh-Hans-CN">
            作为 Saber 的开发者，我非常高兴地向您介绍一款彻底改变您记笔记方式的应用程序。Saber 是一款终极手写笔记应用程序，旨在将您的笔记体验提升到新的高度！这款功能丰富的应用程序以尖端技术为动力，让您尽情享受手写的艺术，释放您的创造力。Saber 的界面直观、现代，可轻松记下笔记、绘制图表或精确注释 PDF。
        </p>
        <p xml:lang="zh-Hans-CN">
            当我开始制作电子笔记时，我找不到任何符合我要求的私有开源应用程序，因此我最终不得不使用一个专有应用程序。我决定创建 Saber，让人们可以选择一款值得信赖的私有开源应用程序。Saber 是完全开源的，这意味着任何人都可以审核代码，以确保其安全性和私密性。Saber 会对您的数据进行加密，并可以同步到您选择的任何兼容服务器，让您完全掌控自己的数据。
        </p>
        <p xml:lang="zh-Hans-CN">
            您是否喜欢在平板电脑上做笔记，然后将其传输到电脑上？或者您更喜欢在笔记本电脑上输入笔记，然后在平板电脑上批注？无论您的工作流程是什么，Saber 都能为您提供多平台支持，让您随时随地在任何设备上访问您的笔记。Saber 支持 Android、iOS、Windows、macOS 和 Linux，您的笔记会在所有设备上自动同步。如果您处于离线状态，Saber 会在您重新上线时自动同步您的笔记。
        </p>
        <p xml:lang="zh-Hans-CN">
            Saber 是您用过的最好的电子荧光笔。您是否曾经需要突出多行，但又讨厌荧光笔重叠和变色的方式？Saber 采用先进的图形处理技术来处理重叠和保持笔的颜色一致性，为您带来比传统纸张更好的荧光笔使用体验。
        </p>
        <p xml:lang="zh-Hans-CN">
            Saber 可以满足您整理笔记的一切需求。您可以随心所欲地创建文件夹内的文件夹，嵌套文件夹的数量不受限制。即使笔记可能深埋在嵌套文件夹中，您仍然可以通过主屏幕上的最新笔记轻松访问它。
        </p>
        <p xml:lang="zh-Hans-CN">
            在暗黑模式下，Saber 可以智能地反转您的笔记。这意味着您可以在暗光模式下体验整个笔记体验，包括您的图像，从而在低光照环境下获得舒缓而连贯的界面。
        </p>
        <p xml:lang="zh-Hans-CN">
            使用 Saber，探索一种全新的方式来捕捉和组织您的想法。无论您是学生、专业人士还是创意人士，Saber 都是您值得信赖的数字手写工具。立即下载，让您的创意自由流淌！
        </p>

        <p xml:lang="zh-Hant-TW">
            Saber是一個專為手寫而生的筆記應用程式。
        </p>
        <p xml:lang="zh-Hant-TW">
            它被設計得盡可能簡單和直觀，同時仍提供您實際會使用的獨特功能。此外，Saber可以在您所有的設備上使用，無論大小，並在它們之間無縫同步。
        </p>
        <p xml:lang="zh-Hant-TW">
            值得注意的是，當您處於深色模式時，它可以反轉您的筆記。這使您可以在黑色背景上用白色墨水書寫，這在低光源環境下，例如老師在課堂上關燈時，對眼睛更加友好。圖片和PDF文件也會反轉，因此您仍然可以使用數位教科書而無需煩惱。
        </p>
        <p xml:lang="zh-Hant-TW">
            Saber使用雙密碼系統來保護您的筆記，使其只能被您存取，即使有人對伺服器擁有完全控制權也是如此。您可以安全地將筆記存儲在官方的Saber伺服器上，或者是其他伺服器，甚至是自己搭建！
        </p>
        <p xml:lang="zh-Hant-TW">
            本應用程式是完全開源的，任何人都可以查看原始碼，了解它的具體運作方式以及如何處理您的資料。許多其他筆記應用程式是閉源和專有的，這意味著它們的內部運作對公眾來說是一個謎。
        </p>
        <p xml:lang="zh-Hant-TW">
            作為一名數學生，我在其他應用中經常遇到的問題之一是，使用其他應用時，突出顯示多行方程總是很麻煩，因為突出顯示在重疊時會改變顏色。我遇到的另一個問題是，在某些應用程式中，突出顯示會在文字上方渲染，將其淡化，使其難以閱讀。Saber的突出顯示沒有這些問題。它使用的畫布合成技術以一種優於傳統紙張相一致的方式呈現突出顯示，在處理重疊時保持顏色一致。
        </p>
        <p xml:lang="zh-Hant-TW">
            Saber具有使筆記井井有條所需的一切功能。在無限嵌套的資料夾中創建資料夾，盡情發揮您的創意，而且對於嵌套資料夾的數量沒有限制。即使筆記可能深藏在嵌套的資料夾中，您仍然可以輕鬆存取，因為最近的筆記始終顯示在主螢幕上。
        </p>
        <p xml:lang="zh-Hant-TW">
            透過Saber，發現一種全新的捕捉和組織思緒的方式。無論您是學生、專業人士還是具有創造力的思維者，Saber都是您在數位手寫中信賴的伙伴。立即下載，讓您的思想自由流暢！
        </p>

    </description>

    <launchable type="desktop-id">com.adilhanney.saber.desktop</launchable>

    <content_rating type="oars-1.1" />

    <categories>
        <category>Education</category>
        <category>Graphics</category>
        <category>Office</category>
    </categories>

    <keywords>
        <keyword>cross-platform</keyword>
        <keyword>handwritten</keyword>
        <keyword>notes</keyword>
    </keywords>

    <screenshots>
        <!--
        DO NOT EDIT.
        Any modifications will be overwritten.
        This <screenshots/> tag is generated by bump_version.dart.
        -->
        <screenshot type="default">
            <caption>The home screen showing your recent notes</caption>
            <image>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/saber-notes/saber/refs/tags/v1.33.2/metadata/en-US/images/flathubScreenshots/1_home.png</image>
            <image xml:lang="ar">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/saber-notes/saber/refs/tags/v1.33.2/metadata/ar/images/flathubScreenshots/1_home.png</image>
            <image xml:lang="ca">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/saber-notes/saber/refs/tags/v1.33.2/metadata/ca/images/flathubScreenshots/1_home.png</image>
            <image xml:lang="cs">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/saber-notes/saber/refs/tags/v1.33.2/metadata/cs/images/flathubScreenshots/1_home.png</image>
            <image xml:lang="de">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/saber-notes/saber/refs/tags/v1.33.2/metadata/de/images/flathubScreenshots/1_home.png</image>
            <image xml:lang="eo">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/saber-notes/saber/refs/tags/v1.33.2/metadata/eo/images/flathubScreenshots/1_home.png</image>
            <image xml:lang="es">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/saber-notes/saber/refs/tags/v1.33.2/metadata/es/images/flathubScreenshots/1_home.png</image>
            <image xml:lang="fa">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/saber-notes/saber/refs/tags/v1.33.2/metadata/fa/images/flathubScreenshots/1_home.png</image>
            <image xml:lang="fr">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/saber-notes/saber/refs/tags/v1.33.2/metadata/fr/images/flathubScreenshots/1_home.png</image>
            <image xml:lang="he">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/saber-notes/saber/refs/tags/v1.33.2/metadata/he/images/flathubScreenshots/1_home.png</image>
            <image xml:lang="hu">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/saber-notes/saber/refs/tags/v1.33.2/metadata/hu/images/flathubScreenshots/1_home.png</image>
            <image xml:lang="it">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/saber-notes/saber/refs/tags/v1.33.2/metadata/it/images/flathubScreenshots/1_home.png</image>
            <image xml:lang="pl">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/saber-notes/saber/refs/tags/v1.33.2/metadata/pl/images/flathubScreenshots/1_home.png</image>
            <image xml:lang="pt-BR">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/saber-notes/saber/refs/tags/v1.33.2/metadata/pt-BR/images/flathubScreenshots/1_home.png</image>
            <image xml:lang="ru">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/saber-notes/saber/refs/tags/v1.33.2/metadata/ru/images/flathubScreenshots/1_home.png</image>
            <image xml:lang="sl">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/saber-notes/saber/refs/tags/v1.33.2/metadata/sl/images/flathubScreenshots/1_home.png</image>
            <image xml:lang="th">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/saber-notes/saber/refs/tags/v1.33.2/metadata/th/images/flathubScreenshots/1_home.png</image>
            <image xml:lang="tr">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/saber-notes/saber/refs/tags/v1.33.2/metadata/tr/images/flathubScreenshots/1_home.png</image>
            <image xml:lang="vi">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/saber-notes/saber/refs/tags/v1.33.2/metadata/vi/images/flathubScreenshots/1_home.png</image>
        </screenshot>
        <screenshot>
            <caption>The editor showing some notes from a maths lecture</caption>
            <image>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/saber-notes/saber/refs/tags/v1.33.2/metadata/en-US/images/flathubScreenshots/2_editor.png</image>
            <image xml:lang="ar">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/saber-notes/saber/refs/tags/v1.33.2/metadata/ar/images/flathubScreenshots/2_editor.png</image>
            <image xml:lang="ca">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/saber-notes/saber/refs/tags/v1.33.2/metadata/ca/images/flathubScreenshots/2_editor.png</image>
            <image xml:lang="cs">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/saber-notes/saber/refs/tags/v1.33.2/metadata/cs/images/flathubScreenshots/2_editor.png</image>
            <image xml:lang="de">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/saber-notes/saber/refs/tags/v1.33.2/metadata/de/images/flathubScreenshots/2_editor.png</image>
            <image xml:lang="eo">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/saber-notes/saber/refs/tags/v1.33.2/metadata/eo/images/flathubScreenshots/2_editor.png</image>
            <image xml:lang="es">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/saber-notes/saber/refs/tags/v1.33.2/metadata/es/images/flathubScreenshots/2_editor.png</image>
            <image xml:lang="fa">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/saber-notes/saber/refs/tags/v1.33.2/metadata/fa/images/flathubScreenshots/2_editor.png</image>
            <image xml:lang="fr">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/saber-notes/saber/refs/tags/v1.33.2/metadata/fr/images/flathubScreenshots/2_editor.png</image>
            <image xml:lang="he">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/saber-notes/saber/refs/tags/v1.33.2/metadata/he/images/flathubScreenshots/2_editor.png</image>
            <image xml:lang="hu">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/saber-notes/saber/refs/tags/v1.33.2/metadata/hu/images/flathubScreenshots/2_editor.png</image>
            <image xml:lang="it">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/saber-notes/saber/refs/tags/v1.33.2/metadata/it/images/flathubScreenshots/2_editor.png</image>
            <image xml:lang="pl">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/saber-notes/saber/refs/tags/v1.33.2/metadata/pl/images/flathubScreenshots/2_editor.png</image>
            <image xml:lang="pt-BR">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/saber-notes/saber/refs/tags/v1.33.2/metadata/pt-BR/images/flathubScreenshots/2_editor.png</image>
            <image xml:lang="ru">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/saber-notes/saber/refs/tags/v1.33.2/metadata/ru/images/flathubScreenshots/2_editor.png</image>
            <image xml:lang="sl">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/saber-notes/saber/refs/tags/v1.33.2/metadata/sl/images/flathubScreenshots/2_editor.png</image>
            <image xml:lang="th">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/saber-notes/saber/refs/tags/v1.33.2/metadata/th/images/flathubScreenshots/2_editor.png</image>
            <image xml:lang="tr">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/saber-notes/saber/refs/tags/v1.33.2/metadata/tr/images/flathubScreenshots/2_editor.png</image>
            <image xml:lang="vi">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/saber-notes/saber/refs/tags/v1.33.2/metadata/vi/images/flathubScreenshots/2_editor.png</image>
        </screenshot>
        <screenshot>
            <caption>The login page which asks which Nextcloud server you want to use</caption>
            <image>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/saber-notes/saber/refs/tags/v1.33.2/metadata/en-US/images/flathubScreenshots/3_login.png</image>
            <image xml:lang="ar">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/saber-notes/saber/refs/tags/v1.33.2/metadata/ar/images/flathubScreenshots/3_login.png</image>
            <image xml:lang="ca">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/saber-notes/saber/refs/tags/v1.33.2/metadata/ca/images/flathubScreenshots/3_login.png</image>
            <image xml:lang="cs">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/saber-notes/saber/refs/tags/v1.33.2/metadata/cs/images/flathubScreenshots/3_login.png</image>
            <image xml:lang="de">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/saber-notes/saber/refs/tags/v1.33.2/metadata/de/images/flathubScreenshots/3_login.png</image>
            <image xml:lang="eo">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/saber-notes/saber/refs/tags/v1.33.2/metadata/eo/images/flathubScreenshots/3_login.png</image>
            <image xml:lang="es">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/saber-notes/saber/refs/tags/v1.33.2/metadata/es/images/flathubScreenshots/3_login.png</image>
            <image xml:lang="fa">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/saber-notes/saber/refs/tags/v1.33.2/metadata/fa/images/flathubScreenshots/3_login.png</image>
            <image xml:lang="fr">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/saber-notes/saber/refs/tags/v1.33.2/metadata/fr/images/flathubScreenshots/3_login.png</image>
            <image xml:lang="he">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/saber-notes/saber/refs/tags/v1.33.2/metadata/he/images/flathubScreenshots/3_login.png</image>
            <image xml:lang="hu">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/saber-notes/saber/refs/tags/v1.33.2/metadata/hu/images/flathubScreenshots/3_login.png</image>
            <image xml:lang="it">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/saber-notes/saber/refs/tags/v1.33.2/metadata/it/images/flathubScreenshots/3_login.png</image>
            <image xml:lang="pl">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/saber-notes/saber/refs/tags/v1.33.2/metadata/pl/images/flathubScreenshots/3_login.png</image>
            <image xml:lang="pt-BR">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/saber-notes/saber/refs/tags/v1.33.2/metadata/pt-BR/images/flathubScreenshots/3_login.png</image>
            <image xml:lang="ru">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/saber-notes/saber/refs/tags/v1.33.2/metadata/ru/images/flathubScreenshots/3_login.png</image>
            <image xml:lang="sl">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/saber-notes/saber/refs/tags/v1.33.2/metadata/sl/images/flathubScreenshots/3_login.png</image>
            <image xml:lang="th">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/saber-notes/saber/refs/tags/v1.33.2/metadata/th/images/flathubScreenshots/3_login.png</image>
            <image xml:lang="tr">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/saber-notes/saber/refs/tags/v1.33.2/metadata/tr/images/flathubScreenshots/3_login.png</image>
            <image xml:lang="vi">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/saber-notes/saber/refs/tags/v1.33.2/metadata/vi/images/flathubScreenshots/3_login.png</image>
        </screenshot>
        <screenshot>
            <caption>The settings page showing that the user is now logged in</caption>
            <image>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/saber-notes/saber/refs/tags/v1.33.2/metadata/en-US/images/flathubScreenshots/4_settings.png</image>
            <image xml:lang="ar">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/saber-notes/saber/refs/tags/v1.33.2/metadata/ar/images/flathubScreenshots/4_settings.png</image>
            <image xml:lang="ca">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/saber-notes/saber/refs/tags/v1.33.2/metadata/ca/images/flathubScreenshots/4_settings.png</image>
            <image xml:lang="cs">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/saber-notes/saber/refs/tags/v1.33.2/metadata/cs/images/flathubScreenshots/4_settings.png</image>
            <image xml:lang="de">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/saber-notes/saber/refs/tags/v1.33.2/metadata/de/images/flathubScreenshots/4_settings.png</image>
            <image xml:lang="eo">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/saber-notes/saber/refs/tags/v1.33.2/metadata/eo/images/flathubScreenshots/4_settings.png</image>
            <image xml:lang="es">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/saber-notes/saber/refs/tags/v1.33.2/metadata/es/images/flathubScreenshots/4_settings.png</image>
            <image xml:lang="fa">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/saber-notes/saber/refs/tags/v1.33.2/metadata/fa/images/flathubScreenshots/4_settings.png</image>
            <image xml:lang="fr">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/saber-notes/saber/refs/tags/v1.33.2/metadata/fr/images/flathubScreenshots/4_settings.png</image>
            <image xml:lang="he">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/saber-notes/saber/refs/tags/v1.33.2/metadata/he/images/flathubScreenshots/4_settings.png</image>
            <image xml:lang="hu">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/saber-notes/saber/refs/tags/v1.33.2/metadata/hu/images/flathubScreenshots/4_settings.png</image>
            <image xml:lang="it">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/saber-notes/saber/refs/tags/v1.33.2/metadata/it/images/flathubScreenshots/4_settings.png</image>
            <image xml:lang="pl">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/saber-notes/saber/refs/tags/v1.33.2/metadata/pl/images/flathubScreenshots/4_settings.png</image>
            <image xml:lang="pt-BR">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/saber-notes/saber/refs/tags/v1.33.2/metadata/pt-BR/images/flathubScreenshots/4_settings.png</image>
            <image xml:lang="ru">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/saber-notes/saber/refs/tags/v1.33.2/metadata/ru/images/flathubScreenshots/4_settings.png</image>
            <image xml:lang="sl">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/saber-notes/saber/refs/tags/v1.33.2/metadata/sl/images/flathubScreenshots/4_settings.png</image>
            <image xml:lang="th">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/saber-notes/saber/refs/tags/v1.33.2/metadata/th/images/flathubScreenshots/4_settings.png</image>
            <image xml:lang="tr">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/saber-notes/saber/refs/tags/v1.33.2/metadata/tr/images/flathubScreenshots/4_settings.png</image>
            <image xml:lang="vi">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/saber-notes/saber/refs/tags/v1.33.2/metadata/vi/images/flathubScreenshots/4_settings.png</image>
        </screenshot>
    </screenshots>

    <releases>
        <release version="1.33.2" type="development" date="2026-04-16">
            <description>
                <ul>
                    <li>Minor code cleanup and internationalization work. Added scripts to autogenerate Flathub metadata for each language.</li>
                </ul>
            </description>
        </release>
        <release version="1.33.1" type="development" date="2026-04-11">
            <description>
                <ul>
                  <li>Added Polish and Catalan translations</li>
                  <li>Added a confirmation prompt when deleting notes</li>
                  <li>Allowed undoing/redoing changing the background pattern</li>
                  <li>Fixed a bug where changing the background pattern didn't trigger an autosave</li>
                </ul>
            </description>
        </release>
        <release version="1.33.0" type="development" date="2026-04-01">
            <description>
                <ul>
                    <li>Feature: You can now export the current page as a PNG</li>
                    <li>Fixed: Hyperlegible font didn't work with KDE theming</li>
                    <li>Fixed: Indiscriminately using the Ubuntu font in certain parts of the UI</li>
                    <li>Fixed: Parts of the settings page were incorrectly bolded.</li>
                    <li>Fixed: Sync progress indicator was getting stuck when a transfer fails</li>
                    <li>Tweak: Reduced frequency of retrying failed sync transfers</li>
                </ul>
            </description>
        </release>
        <release version="1.32.0" type="development" date="2026-03-21">
            <description>
                <ul>
                    <li>Saber now uses colors from your KDE/COSMIC theme on Linux</li>
                    <li>Increased precision of inverting filter</li>
                    <li>Added a Vietnamese translation</li>
                </ul>
            </description>
        </release>
        <release version="1.31.1" type="development" date="2026-02-16">
            <description>
                <ul>
                    <li>Fixed the wrong PDF page being preloaded</li>
                </ul>
            </description>
        </release>
        <release version="1.31.0" type="development" date="2026-02-14">
            <description>
                <ul>
                    <li>Fixed externally deleted notes still showing up in recent notes</li>
                    <li>Updated to Flutter 3.41</li>
                </ul>
            </description>
        </release>
        <release version="1.30.0" type="development" date="2026-02-01">
            <description>
                <ul>
                    <li>Added a Thai translation by Anucha Hlownonkor</li>
                    <li>Added a Slovenian translation by Tadej Pusnik</li>
                    <li>If a note is in read-only mode, you'll now see the reason why</li>
                </ul>
            </description>
        </release>
        <release version="1.29.5" type="development" date="2026-01-19">
            <description>
                <ul>
                    <li>Fixed being able to name notes with invalid characters. The new rules assist cross-platform compatibility.</li>
                    <li>Imperceptibly tweaked the Saber icon.</li>
                </ul>
            </description>
        </release>
        <release version="1.29.4" type="development" date="2026-01-09">
            <description>
                <ul>
                    <li>Fixed the text cursor showing up in PDF exports.</li>
                    <li>Fixed text editor bugginess after exporting a note.</li>
                    <li>Fixed some resources not being freed up after exporting a note.</li>
                    <li>Restyled the "simplified home layout" as a proper grid view.</li>
                    <li>Fixed some small visual inconsistencies like the border radius of thumbnails.</li>
                </ul>
            </description>
        </release>
        <release version="1.29.3" type="development" date="2025-12-31">
            <description>
                <p>
                    Fixed lots of bugs in the text editor that occured after an auto-save.
                </p>
            </description>
        </release>
        <release version="1.29.2" type="development" date="2025-12-28">
            <description>
                <ul>
                    <li>Page numbers now respect your Atkinson Hyperlegible font setting</li>
                    <li>Migrated AppImage builds to the `linuxdeploy` tool instead of the unmaintained `appimage-builder`.</li>
                </ul>
            </description>
        </release>
        <release version="1.29.1" type="development" date="2025-12-14">
            <description>
                <ul>
                    <li>Home screen cards are now bordered instead of shadowed.</li>
                    <li>Made `https://` optional in the Nextcloud URL field.</li>
                </ul>
            </description>
        </release>
        <release version="1.29.0" type="development" date="2025-11-20">
            <description>
                <ul>
                    <li>Big improvements for Onyx Boox devices with increased tool support and miscellaneous fixes thanks to zinstack625 on GitHub.</li>
                    <li>Improved speed of PDF imports.</li>
                    <li>Improved loading times for notes containing large PDFs (they're now loaded page by page rather than all at once).</li>
                    <li>Fixed an issue with saving PDFs from the long-press dialog.</li>
                    <li>Fixed a bug where the wrong tool would be selected when turning off the eraser, thanks to ComputerElite on GitHub.</li>
                </ul>
            </description>
        </release>
        <release version="1.28.2" type="development" date="2025-11-15">
            <description>
                <ul>
                    <li>To improve ease of use, finger-drawing is automatically disabled if you use a stylus. You can turn off this feature in Settings.</li>
                    <li>You can now zoom with a mouse by holding the Control or Command key while scrolling.</li>
                    <li>Fixed strokes from the shape pen getting smushed when you finish drawing them.</li>
                    <li>Improved the accuracy of the lower quality strokes that are shown when zoomed out.</li>
                    <li>Fixed numerical (NaN) errors with some strokes.</li>
                    <li>Updated Flutter to 3.38.</li>
                </ul>
            </description>
        </release>
        <release version="1.28.1" type="development" date="2025-11-11">
            <description>
                <ul>
                    <li>Improved animation smoothness when closing a note.</li>
                    <li>Your mouse wheel now scrolls instead of zooming. Hold the Ctrl key to zoom.</li>
                    <li>Made the New Note button less round.</li>
                </ul>
            </description>
        </release>
        <release version="1.28.0" type="development" date="2025-11-10">
            <description>
                <ul>
                    <li>Added a new floating navigation bar.</li>
                    <li>A pending autosave is now cancelled if you undo all changes.</li>
                    <li>Improved the smoothness of home screen transitions.</li>
                    <li>Fixed some path handling bugs on the browse page.</li>
                </ul>
            </description>
        </release>
        <release version="1.27.2" type="development" date="2025-11-07">
            <description>
                <ul>
                    <li>Fixed the entire app breaking if you choose the Esperanto language.</li>
                    <li>Fixed the navigation bar not updating its text when you change language.</li>
                    <li>Fixed the storage used percentage not being rounded.</li>
                    <li>Freed up memory used by images and PDFs.</li>
                    <li>Removed the pencil sound effect, and removed the sound+microphone flatpak permission.</li>
                </ul>
            </description>
        </release>
        <release version="1.27.1" type="development" date="2025-11-02">
            <description>
                <ul>
                    <li>Various UI improvements.</li>
                    <li>Removed the themed title bar, replacing it with server-side decorations for better KDE support.</li>
                    <li>Delayed showing the app until the first frame is rendered, removing the initial black screen on launch.</li>
                    <li>Resized the app icon to match other Linux apps.</li>
                </ul>
            </description>
        </release>
        <release version="1.27.0" type="development" date="2025-10-30">
            <description>
                <ul>
                    <li>Improved the look of pencil strokes and their rendering performance.</li>
                    <li>Saber now uses a themed title bar (configurable), which responds to light/dark mode changes.</li>
                    <li>Switches are now themed on the Cupertino (iOS-style) theme.</li>
                    <li>Added an Esperanto translation.</li>
                </ul>
            </description>
        </release>
        <release version="1.26.12" type="development" date="2025-10-30">
            <description>
                <ul>
                    <li>Bumped the version to 1.x to reflect the maturity of the app and to let version numbers be more meaningful.</li>
                </ul>
            </description>
        </release>
    </releases>
</component>
